Guide to the Duke Family papers on the Duke Farms residence, 1859-2004 and undated RL.01437
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Records, 1859-2004 and undated
  - Deeds, Mortgages, and Agreements relating to the formation of J.B. Duke’s Hillsborough, N.J. property. 1859–1937, 1946 (2 of 4) (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Deeds, Mortgages, and Agreements relating to the formation of J.B. Duke’s Hillsborough, N.J. property. 1859–1937, 1946 (3 of 4) (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Deeds, Mortgages, and Agreements relating to the formation of J.B. Duke’s Hillsborough, N.J. property. 1859–1937, 1946 (4 of 4) (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Assignments of Mortgages and Bond relating to the Estate of Eliza Brokaw, Deceased. 1881, 1884, 1890, 1906 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Agreements which sold land from one owner to another. This land eventually became part of Duke Farms. Includes Proxy for representation at a State Trust Company of New York meeting. 1882, 1893, 1896, 1896, 1913 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Proposal submitted to Mr. J.B. Duke from American Water Softener Company for the installation of filters at Duke Farms. Signed by J.B. Duke. March 29, 1909 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Articles of Agreement between J.B. Duke and Lord & Burnham Company for the erection of a range of greenhouses at Duke Farms, N.J. June 8, 1909 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Lease Agreement between J.B. Duke and Louisa D. Elmendorf’s use of land on Duke Farms (March 24, 1911). Also includes Agreement for the sale of property to J.B. Duke (October 1, 1910). 1910–1911 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Article of Agreement between J.B. Duke and Lord and Burnham Company that states the latter’s payment of $56,000 for the completion of a range of fruit houses in accordance with Plan No. 4724. 1912 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Articles of Agreement between John Ditmas and J.B. Duke transferring ownership of Ditmas Farm to Duke. June 27, 1916 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Deeds and Schedule of Deeds dated May 1, 1917 by J.B. Duke and wife to Duke Farms Company. 1917 (1 of 2) (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Deeds and Schedule of Deeds dated May 1, 1917 by J.B. Duke and wife to Duke Farms Company. 1917 (2 of 2) (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Certificate of Steam Boiler Inspection, Duke Farms Co. Inc. September 20, 1918 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Fidelity and Guaranty Company Continuation Certificate in the sum of $1,000 on behalf of Duke Farms Co., Inc. in favor of Wm. G. McAdoo, Dr. Gen. of RR & Philadelphia Reading Railroad Co. 1919 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Agreement between Public Service Electric Co., N.Y. Telephone Co., and Duke Farms Company (1920) covering the use of poles on Duke Farms property. File includes related correspondence and other Agreements for electrical service. 1920–1921, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Warranty Deed conveying Duke Farms Company to Doris Duke Cromwell. November 5, 1941 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Lease between Doris Duke and the U.S.A. (Veterans Administration) for the use of 3 tracts of land at Duke Farms. Land was then donated (51.597 acres) in 1968. File also includes letters relating to donation. Includes copy of Indenture between Doris Duke and U.S.A. (November 27, 1968). 1947, 1968–1970 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Agreements between Doris Duke and the Somerset County Park Commission, re the sale of stock of the Raritan Water Power Co. File includes related correspondence. 1959, 1968, 1972–1973 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Lease Agreement between Doris Duke and Michael Tacak for lease of the Kaufman Horse Barn and Building No. 75. 1976–1979 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Lease Agreement between Doris Duke and Michael Tacak for lease of the Kaufman Horse Barn. Includes related materials. Also, includes Lease from lessee, Alex Bicker, for the same barn in 1976. 1976–1980 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Consent to place fourteen poles and anchors adjacent to the Duke Farms property along South Branch Rd., known as Block 144, Lots 18 and 19. November 29, 1978 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Agreements and correspondence relating to Doris Duke’s Leases with tenants in homes on Duke Farms. 1978 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Lease Agreements between Doris Duke and J. Preston Quick and between Doris Duke and Mr. and Mrs. Hansson for House No. 120. 1978–1979 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Lease Agreement and related materials concerning Lisa and Mike Gilreaths’ rental of House No. 120 with the Estate of Doris Duke. Before the Gilreaths, there is a Lease between Eva and John Tuite with Doris Duke and before the Tuites, there is a Lease with Burnett Deyerle. Before the Deyerles, there is a Lease with Susan and Lawrence Hisko. Before the Hiskos, Lease is with Hanssons. 1978–1998 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Lease Agreements between Doris Duke and Ever Lea Farms, Inc. for lease of the Davis Farm. 1979–1982 (1 of 2) (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Lease Agreements between Doris Duke and Ever Lea Farms, Inc. for lease of the Davis Farm. 1979–1982 (2 of 2) (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Lease Agreements between Doris Duke and James Norz for Field Nos. 22, 24, and 25 (approximately 25 acres). 1979–1984 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Sample Lease forms between Doris Duke and prospective lessees. 1980s (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Agreement to convey between County of Somerset and Doris Duke and other documents related to Easements to be acquired for New Centre Road Bridge, Hillsborough. 1980 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Lease Agreements between Doris Duke and Richard Norz for Field No. 37 (40 acres in the Lowlands). 1980–1985 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Lease Agreement between Doris Duke and William Singer/David Codling for the lease of House No. 52B. Includes related materials. 1981–1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Lease Agreements between Doris Duke and J. Preston Quick Jr. for the lease of Field Nos. 22, 24, 25, and 27. Includes related materials. 1981–1989 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Lease and related materials concerning Ron David’s lease of House No. 74, barn, 6 farm buildings, 100+ acres of pasture lands, and ‘riding area’ with the Estate of Doris Duke. 1981–1996 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Deeds, Affidavit of Title, and related materials for an Easement conveyance executed by Doris Duke for a Beckman Lane Improvement (Block 150, Lots 1 & 1A). 1982–1984 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Indenture and Easement between Doris Duke and the Elizabethtown Water Company. 1982–1984 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Lease Agreement between Doris Duke and Eric Fox for lease of House No. 49B. Includes related materials. 1982, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Lease Agreement between Doris Duke and Franco Rossellini for House No. 49. 1983 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Lease Agreements between Doris Duke and Singer/Codling for House No. 52B, between Doris Duke and Mr. & Mrs. Barrett for House No. 87 and between Doris Duke and Eva and John Tuite for House No. 120. 1983–1984 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Lease Agreements between Doris Duke and Mr. & Mrs. M. Kovonok for the lease of House No. 87. File includes other related materials. 1983–1985 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Lease Agreements between Doris Duke and Ever Lea Farms, Inc. for approximately 147–319 acres on Duke Farms over the course of several years. 1983–1986 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Housing policy and sample Lease. 1984–1986 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Legal materials, including Leases, Contracts for sale, and Deeds relating to Doris Duke’s purchase of 2 parcels of land, “Railroad Right of Way Property” from Central Jersey Industries at public auction in October 1985. File also includes related correspondence and discussions of demolishing the defunct railroad bridge spanning the South Branch of the Raritan River (from DBO Safe). 1985–1986 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Insurance policies and related materials concerning shipments of rugs from China to Duke Farms. 1986 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Lease Agreement between Doris Duke and Mr. & Mrs. Kent for lease of House No. 52B. 1986 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Lease Agreement between Doris Duke and Greer S. Imbrie for the lease of House No. 52A. Other materials relate to Rosalind La Roche’s rental of the same house, a few years earlier. 1986–1987 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Lease Agreement and related materials concerning the lease of House No. 49A to Mr. and Mrs. Kent. 1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Lease Agreement between Doris Duke and Joyce Reels for the lease of House No. 52B. 1987, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Various insurance coverages and Workmen’s Compensation Policy. 1987–1991 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Insurance claims against Duke Farms, re: rotten tree falling on car. 1988 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Lease Agreement between Doris Duke and Christine Ulanowski for lease of House No. 49B. File includes related correspondence, photos, and keys. 1989 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Lease Agreement and related materials for Donald Quick’s lease of 75 acres on New Center Road. Agreements were made with the Estate of Doris Duke. The 75 acres are part of the Beekman Homestead Farm (1995–1996). 1992–1997 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Title Commitment, Duke Estate property, Chicago Title Insurance Company (Transferred to DDCF Archives from the Office of T. Taylor, October, 2005). 1994 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Lease Agreement and related materials between Ann Terry (Savoye) and the Estate of Doris Duke for House No. 52A. 1995–1996, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Lease Agreement and notice of past due rental payments and/or lease expiration to Donald Quick, Mr. and Mrs. Gilreath, and Carlos Metz. 1996–1997 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Lease Agreement and related materials between Carlos Metz and the Estate of Doris Duke for Cottage 9. 1996, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Inventory, Marble statuary. n.d. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Lists of amount of coal burned in greenhouses, plants & flowers sold, and Analysis of Profit and Loss accounts. 1912–1913 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Appraisal values for structures at Duke Farms as well as equipment, furniture, and farm-related tools. 1927 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Reports and related materials concerning the Power House at Duke Farms. 1938–1942 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Inventory of stable equipment. 1942, 1970, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Real estate appraisal of Duke Farms after storm damage. 1954, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Various appraisals, mainly of Duke Farms. File also includes a map of Duke Island Park. 1954, 1972–1987 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Proposals and related materials for potential jobs at Duke Farms. 1957–1986 (1 of 2) (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Proposals and related materials for potential jobs at Duke Farms. 1957–1986 (2 of 2) (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Appraisal, Duke Farms property value for the period, October 10, 1915–January 31, 1959. c. 1959 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Employees’ telephone list. 1967 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Status report on Duke Farms happenings during Doris Duke’s absence from the property. circa 1970s–early 1980s (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Log book from one of the DBO secretaries. 1971–1973 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Studies, reports, and related materials concerning the alignment of Auten Road and environmental effects to Duke Farms. 1976, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Inventories and estimates of farm production including hay. 1978–1980 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Inventory of maps and plans. c. 1987 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - List of record boxes created during Doris Duke’s lifetime. 1989–1990 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Telephone list for Residence and other locations. c. 1990–1991 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Reports, Market Rent Analysis for 28 residences on estate and property leased by Ron David. 1994–1996 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Report and related materials created by John Newhall, former Farm Manager. 1997 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Specifications, for construction of Reservoir Embankment (November 23, 1896); Specifications for the Laying of Drains from catch-basins (June 30, 1897). 1896–1897 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Specification, Greenhouses for Mr. J.B. Duke. Architect, Horace Trumbauer, Philadelphia, PA. 1909 (2 sets) (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Specifications, for laying vitrified pipe on the Estate of J.B. Duke. 1909 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Notes by Louis Miller relating to Mr. Duke’s instructions for cutting clay soil from Lake No. 27 and other notations for Lake Nos. 28 and 5. July 5, 1910 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Specifications, Old Foundation. Specifications, Trumbauer. 1911 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Narrative, background on Duke family and Duke Farms. c. 1930s (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Specification, for Alteration to Boat House at Duke Farms, Wyeth & King. June 1938 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Articles relating to Eweson Bio-Conservation system and the possibility of employing such a system at Duke Farms. 1977 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Articles relating to STC Oil Storage Facility, Roycefield Road. November 1980–January 1981 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Proposals, clippings, and restaurant menus. 1987–1989 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Printed materials sent to Doris Duke from various consultants soliciting business. Consultants include landscape illuminators, security professionals, and water specialists. 1991–1992 (1 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Printed materials sent to Doris Duke from various consultants soliciting business. Consultants include landscape illuminators, security professionals, and water specialists. 1991–1992 (2 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Copy of a Christie’s catalog page for a Minolta camera located in the DBO. March 27, 1997 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Old Accounts. 1953–1956 (Oversize-box 65)
  - Accounts, general sales, unsettled and farm. 1947–1960 (Oversize-box 66)
  - Cashbook, cash received. 1947–1953 (Oversize-box 67)
  - General Ledger. 1957–1960 (Oversize-box 68)
  - General Ledger. 1953 (Oversize-box 69)
  - Disbursements. 1984–1986 (Oversize-box 70)
  - Disbursements. 1983 (Oversize-box 71)
  - Farm Records & Inventories. 1967–1973 (Oversize-box 72)
  - General Ledger. 1947–1948 (Oversize-box 73)
  - General Ledger. 1949 (Oversize-box 74)
  - Plumbing Inventory. 1959–1960 (Oversize-box 75)
  - Mechanic, Electrician, and Mason’s Inventory. 1959–1960 (Oversize-box 76)
  - General Ledger. 1951 (Oversize-box 77)
  - General Ledger. 1954 (Oversize-box 78)
  - Administrative Expenses. 1982 (Oversize-box 79)
  - Farm Records, dairy, field crops, park, guard force, and maintenance. 1983 (Oversize-box 79)
  - General Ledger. 1950 (Oversize-box 80)
  - Sales Register. 1950–1953 (Oversize-box 81)
  - General Ledger. 1947 (Oversize-box 82)
  - General Ledger. 1985 (Oversize-box 83)
  - Farm Records, dairy and field crops. 1975–1981 (Oversize-box 84)
  - Farm Records, dairy, field crops, park, guard force, and maintenance. 1982 (Oversize-box 85)
  - Ledger No. 2. 1940–1946 (Oversize-box 86)
  - Cashbook. December 1968–April 1983 (Oversize-box 87)
  - Farms Records, administration, guard force, maintenance, and gasohol. 1975–1981 (Oversize-box 88)
  - Insurance Ledger. 1947–1952 (Oversize-box 89)
  - Cashbook, miscellaneous sales. 1898–1905 (Oversize-box 90)
  - General Ledger. 1984 (Oversize-box 90)
  - Journal. 1975–1978, 1978 Dec-1983 (Oversize-box 90)
  - Journal. 1969–1974 (Oversize-box 90)
  - Cash Receipts. 1983–1985 (Oversize-box 90)
  - Rental Records. 1983–1984 (Oversize-box 90)
  - Voucher Register. 1950–1955 (Oversize-box 91)
  - General Ledger. 1954–1957 (Oversize-box 92)
  - Ledger & Voucher Register. 1975–1980 (Oversize-box 93)
  - General Ledger. 1957–1963 (Oversize-box 94)
  - General Ledger. 1952 (Oversize-box 95)
  - Ledger No. 4. 1912–1917 (Oversize-box 96)
  - Journal No. 1. October 1927–May 1933 (Oversize-box 97)
  - Ledger No. 3. 1904–1911 (Oversize-box 98)
  - Residence Expenses. 1975–1977 (Oversize-box 99)
  - Park Expenses. 1976–1981 (Oversize-box 100)
  - Cashbook No. 11. August 1909–May 1910 (Oversize-box 101)
  - Cashbook No. 2. November 1897–October 1899 (Oversize-box 102)
  - Ledger No. 2. 1897–1903 (Oversize-box 103)
  - Cashbook No. 3. November 1899–April 1901 (Oversize-box 104)
  - Journal No. 3. January 1939–June 1943 (Oversize-box 105)
  - Statement of Accounts (Including N.H. Duke). 1930–1942 (Oversize-box 106)
  - Statement of Accounts (Including N.H. Duke). 1931–1947 (Oversize-box 106)
  - Journal No.1 (Duke Farms Company). April 1917–July 1921 (Oversize-box 107)
  - Journal No. 4. July 1943–December 1946 (Oversize-box 108)
  - Journal No. 2. October 1897–December 1904 (Oversize-box 109)
  - Cashbook No. 4. May 1901–October 1902 (Oversize-box 110)
  - Cashbook No. 13. May 1911–March 1912 (Oversize-box 111)
  - Cashbook No. 6. May 1904–June 1905 (Oversize-box 112)
  - Cashbook No. 7. July 1905–May 1906 (Oversize-box 113)
  - Journal No. 2. June 1933–December 1938 (Oversize-box 114)
  - Journal No. 1 (J.B.D.). October 1893–October 1897 (Oversize-box 115)
  - Cashbook No. 1 (J.B.D.). October 1893–October 1897 (Oversize-box 116)
  - Ledger No. 1 (Duke Farms Company). 1917–1922 (Oversize-box 117)
  - Cashbook No. 9. August 1907–September 1908 (Oversize-box 118)
  - Ledger No. 1 (J.B.D.). 1893–1897 (Oversize-box 119)
  - Cashbook No. 17. October 1915–April 1917 (Oversize-box 120)
  - Cashbook No. 12. June 1910–April 1911 (Oversize-box 121)
  - Cashbook. 1961–1968 (Oversize-box 122)
  - Cash Receipts. January 1976–September 1980 (Oversize-box 123)
  - Cash Receipts. October 1980–May 1983 (Oversize-box 123)
  - Journal. 1920–1922 (Oversize-box 124)
  - Journal. 1923 (Oversize-box 124)
  - Journal. 1930–1947 (Oversize-box 124)
  - Journal No. 3. January 1905–December 1911 (Oversize-box 125)
  - Journal No. 4. January 1912–May 1917 (Oversize-box 126)
  - Meter Readings. 1953–1963 (2 copies) (Oversize-box 127)
  - Meter Readings. 1963–1965 (Oversize-box 127)
  - Meter Readings. 1965–1968 (Oversize-box 127)
  - Cashbook No. 5. November 1902–April 1904 (Oversize-box 128)
  - Cashbook No. 15. July 1913–September 1914 (Oversize-box 129)
  - Ledger No. 1 (Duke Farm Company). 1922–1927 (Oversize-box 130)
  - Index to Ledger No. 1 (Duke Farm Company). 1922–1927 (Oversize-box 130)
  - Cashbook No. 1 (Duke Farm Company). December 1922–May 1925 (Oversize-box 131)
  - Journal No. 1 (Duke Farm Company). December 1922–August 1927 (Oversize-box 132)
  - Cashbook, sales and deposits. 1963–1964 (Oversize-box 133)
  - Cashbook, sales and deposits. 1965 (Oversize-box 133)
  - Cashbook, sales and deposits. 1966–1967 (Oversize-box 133)
  - Cashbook, sales and deposits. 1968–1969 (Oversize-box 133)
  - Cashbook No. 16. October 1914–September 1915 (Oversize-box 134)
  - Cashbook No. 14. April 1912–June 1913 (Oversize-box 135)
  - Ledger No. 1 (Includes index and inventories). 1927–1939 (Oversize-box 136)
  - Cashbook No. 8. June 1906–July1907 (Oversize-box 137)
  - Journal No. 2 (Duke Farms Company). August 1921–December 1922 (Oversize-box 138)
  - Cashbook No. 10. October 1908–July 1909 (Oversize-box 139)
  - Voucher Record No. 6. May 1945–December 1946 (Oversize-box 140)
  - Voucher Record No. 5. January 1941–July 1945 (Oversize-box 141)
  - Voucher Record No. 2. December 1931–June 1935 (Oversize-box 142)
  - Voucher Record No. 2 (Duke Farms Company). April 1921–December 1923 (Oversize-box 143)
  - Voucher Record No. 1 (Duke Farms Company). May 1917–March 1921 (Oversize-box 144)
  - Voucher Record No. 1. October 1927–December 1931 (Oversize-box 145)
  - Voucher Record No. 4. October 1905–February 1909 (Oversize-box 146)
  - Voucher Record No. 5. 1909–1912 (Oversize-box 147)
  - Voucher Record No. 7. 1915–1916 (Oversize-box 148)
  - Voucher Record No. 2. November 1897–August 1901 (Oversize-box 149)
  - Vouchers. 1958–1964 (Oversize-box 150)
  - Expenses – Residence & Inman Account. 1960–1974 (Oversize-box 151)
  - Miscellaneous Expenses. 1960–1969 (Oversize-box 152)
  - Park, income and expenses. July 1960–December 1975 (Oversize-box 153)
  - Income and Expenses. 1962–1974 (Oversize-box 154)
  - Cashbook No. 2 (Duke Farms Company). 1925–1927 (Oversize-box 155)
  - Cashbook No. 2 (Duke Farms Company). 1919–1921 (Oversize-box 156)
  - Cashbook No. 3 (Duke Farms Company). 1921–1922 (Oversize-box 157)
  - Cashbook No. 5. 1938–1939 (Oversize-box 158)
  - Cashbook No. 4. 1936–1938 (Oversize-box 159)
  - Cashbook No. 3. 1934–1936 (Oversize-box 160)
  - Cashbook No. 1. 1927–1931 (Oversize-box 161)
  - Cashbook No. 6. 1939–1941 (Oversize-box 162)
  - Sales Register. 1954–1957 (Oversize-box 163)
  - Cashbook No. 2. 1931–1934 (Oversize-box 164)
  - Cashbook No. 1 (Duke Farms Company). 1917–1919 (Oversize-box 165)
  - Cashbook No. 7. 1941–1944 (Oversize-box 166)
  - Cashbook No. 8. 1944–1946 (Oversize-box 167)
  - Inventory, Tools and Equipment. 1918–1928 (Oversize-box 168)
  - Inventory, Tools and Equipment. 1943–1946 (Oversize-box 168)
  - Inventory of Animals and Equipment. 1911–1917 (Oversize-box 169)
  - Letterbook. 1916–1917 (Oversize-box 170)
  - Letterbook. 1918–1920 (Oversize-box 171)
  - Letterbook. 1921–1922 (Oversize-box 172)
  - Letterbook. 1924–1925 (Oversize-box 173)
  - Letterbook. 1925–1927 (Oversize-box 173)
  - Letterbook. 1915–1916 (Oversize-box 174)
  - Letterbook. 1914–1915 (Oversize-box 175)
  - Journal. May 1939–February 1943 (Oversize-box 176)
  - Letterbook. March 1913–March 1914 (Oversize-box 177)
  - Social Security Time Books. October 1960–May 1969 (Oversize-box 178)
  - Farm Supplies and Equipment. 1906–1911 (Oversize-box 179)
  - Farm Supplies and Equipment. 1912–1917 (Oversize-box 179)
  - Farm Supplies and Equipment. 1917–1919 (Oversize-box 179)
  - General Ledger. January 1986–October 1987 (Oversize-box 180)
  - General Ledger. November 1987–December 1990 (Oversize-box 180)
  - General Ledger. 1991 (Oversize-box 180)
  - Voucher Record No. 3 (Duke Farms Company). January 1924–August 1927 (Oversize-box 181)
  - Voucher Record No. 3. July 1935–August 1938 (Oversize-box 182)
  - Voucher Record No. 1 (J.B. Duke). October 1893–April 1897 (Oversize-box 183)
  - Voucher Record No. 3. October 1901–July 1905 (Oversize-box 184)
  - Voucher Record No. 6. June 1912–October 1915 (Oversize-box 185)
  - Voucher Record No. 4. August 1938–May 1941 (Oversize-box 186)
  - Raritan Water Power Company Ledger. 1896–1897 (Oversize-box 187)
  - Letter from James A. Innes to Edward F. Loomis. 1892 (Oversize-box 187)
  - Raritan Water Power Company Stock & Real Estate Ledger. 1898–1922 (Oversize-box 188)
  - Management Minutes and other material. 1910–1918 (Oversize-box 188)
  - Raritan Water Power Company Cashbook. 1897–1911 (Oversize-box 189)
  - Raritan Water Power Company Journal. 1897–1930 (Oversize-box 190)
  - Raritan Water Power Company Cashbook. 1911–1927 (Oversize-box 191)
  - Raritan Water Power Company Cashbook. 1927–1940 (Oversize-box 191)
  - Raritan Water Power Company Paybook. 1864–1897 (Oversize-box 192)
  - Raritan Water Power Company Journal. 1896–1897 (Oversize-box 192)
  - Ledger (J.B.D.). 1897–1916 (Oversize-box 193)
  - Flower Sales Ledger. 1931–1935 (Oversize-box 194)
  - Flower Sales Ledger. 1947–1954 (Oversize-box 195)
  - Flower Sales Ledger. 1948–1949 (Oversize-box 196)
  - Journal Vouchers. 1959 (Oversize-box 197)
  - Journal Vouchers. 1961 (Oversize-box 197)
  - General Ledger. 1986 (Oversize-box 198)
  - Voucher Register & Ledger. 1961–1970 (Oversize-box 199)
  - Voucher Register & Ledger. 1970–1974 (Oversize-box 200)
  - Voucher Register & Ledger with Trial Balances. 1981–1983 (Oversize-box 201)
  - General Ledger with Trial Balances. 1987 (Oversize-box 202)
  - Duke Farms Security Journal. January 1982–October 1982 (Oversize-box 203)
  - Duke Farms Security Journal. October 1982–August 1983 (Oversize-box 203)
  - Duke Farms Security Journal. August 1983–June 1984 (Oversize-box 204)
  - Duke Farms Security Journal. June 1984–December 1984 (Oversize-box 204)
  - Indentures and deeds for conveyance of land for Duke Farms. Includes deeds taken from office safe in New York Office, 1864-1960 (Box 237, Folder 1)
  - Somerville Inventory - miscellaneous invoices. Includes purchases by J.B. Duke, 1900-1945 (Box 237, Folder 2)